萝拉是下一位  但她有点难搞
Lola's next, and she's a bit of a biter.
谢谢你同意我观察你一天
Thanks for letting me shadow you today.
-没什么大不了的  亲爱的  -准备好了吗
- Sure, honey. - Ready for this?
实际上  弗雷普  我们已经等了你十年了
Actually, Flip, we've been ready for you for ten years.
别来为难我
Don't bust my chops!
【你这是在助人为乐
You try running a 24-hour convenience store.
这是什么
What is this?
我的肉臼齿  本来的牙掉了
My meat molar! The tooth fell out,
所以我用牛肉干补了一颗
so I made a replacement with some beef jerky.
感谢你让我来参观餐厅
Thanks for letting me check out the restaurant.
当然可以啊  小甜心
Sure thing, hon.
哦  来了一位客人
Ooh, a customer.
嘿  你去试试接待她怎么样
Hey, why don't you take this one?
您的菜  夫人  一份科布沙拉
Here you are, ma'am. One Cobb salad.
嘿  这是怎么回事
Hey, what's the dealio?
我说了要多加培根
I asked for extra bacon.
哦对不起  我的错
Oh, sorry. My bad.
这些蓝芝士的臭味太大了
This blue cheese smells whack.
嘿  为什么这上面有这么多培根
Hey, why is there so much bacon on this?
你在开玩笑吗  伙计
Are you kidding, dude?
好吧  我来帮你解决
Fine, I'll fix it for you!
你知道吗  让我来处理这个亲爱的
Uh, you know what, I got this one, honey.
技术领域看起来真不错  格劳斯爷爷
The tech field seems pretty rad, Mr. Grouse.
谢谢你让我和你待在一起
Thanks for letting me hang with you.
如果你停止摆弄我的桌子
It would be a lot more rad
这会更加不错
if you stopped fiddling with my desk!
我正试图调试这个代码
I'm trying to debug this code.
（画面字）灾难级错误
“灾难级错误”
"Catastrophic error"?
这可真是妙极了
That's the berries.
让我来试试  老兄
Let me give it a try, brah.
（画面字）代码正确
我的妈呀  你是怎么做到的
Holy Toledo. How'd you pull that off?
我猜我通过录制音乐
Guess I learned a thing or two about computers
学了点电脑技术吧
from recording music.
好吧  你在这儿会有前途的  小姐
Well, you've got a future here, young lady.
-真的吗  - 我说是就是
- Really? - You bet ya.
字幕
And it's a heck of a gig.
Great job security and a solid retirement plan!
字幕
Sweet--sounds a lot better than living in a van.
Plus, I see you get Casual Fridays.
字幕
Eeh, casual what now?
Ms. V?
字幕
I just wanted to tell you,
I'm dropping out of the Royal Rumble.
字幕
I know I'm never gonna make it as a rock star,
so I'm done with music.
字幕
I.T. Is my jam now.
It's a heck of a gig.
字幕
Great job security, solid retirement plan.
It's more practical.
字幕
Well, wait, Luna, honey,
you don't have to give up music completely.
字幕
Lots of people play as a hobby.
Nah, it would just break my heart,
字幕
my achy, breaky heart.
Sorry to mess up the Rumble, Ms. V.
字幕
"Chunk &amp; the Pieces"?
- Uh, what's this? - Chester gave me that.
字幕
His band is playing at the Red Herring tonight.
Chunk has a band?
字幕
I thought he gave up music a long time ago.
I'm a little East London
字幕
And I'm a little Royal Woods
When it comes to rock and roll
字幕
I've got the goods
You can call me Chester
字幕
Or you can call me Chunk
Either way, baby
字幕
I've got the funk
Are you ready to get funky?
字幕
All right, let me take it to the rinse cycle!
So that's what he wanted it for.
字幕
Go, Chunk! Rock on!
That was awesome, dude!
字幕
I had no idea you still played.
Yeah, once you get the performing bug,
字幕
you just can't shake it, can ya?
Hey, I know it's none of my biz,
字幕
but that stuff in your yearbook made it seem like
being a rock star was all you ever wanted.
字幕
Are you bummed you didn't make it?
Who says I didn't make it?
字幕
I may not be playing in sold-out arenas,
but I'm doing what I love.
字幕
That's my definition of making it.
Even if you have to live in a van?
字幕
I mean, no offense. It--it's a sweet van.
I don't live in it, love.
字幕
I got me own flat.
What?
字幕
I only sleep in my van the night before a big gig.
Talking of gigs,
字幕
you all sorted for the big Rumble?
- Well, I am now! - Brilliant.
字幕
Just let me know how many guitars you need.
Got the rock and roll bug, and I just can't shake it
字幕
Follow your heart if you really wanna make it
I tried my hand at dental hygiene
字幕
But at the end of the day it just wasn't my scene
You can live your life full of doubt
字幕
Or you can do what you love, and it'll all work out
My life is a dream
字幕
The greatest rock and roll dream
Ladies and gentlemen!
字幕
We've got some Rumble Royalty in the house!
Give it up for Chester "Chunk" Monk!
字幕
You can live your life full of doubt
Or you can do what you love, and it'll all work out
字幕
My life is a dream
The greatest rock and roll dream!